

# Han Wu

Nationality: Chinese Date of birth: 23/06/2002 Phone number: (+86) 13774793237

Email address: wuhan36@mail2.sysu.edu.cn

• Work: Tangqi Road, Xiangzhou District, 519082 Zhuhai (China)

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm a junior student in the School of Software Engineering at Sun Yat-sen University. I'm currently doing some research on AI security in the TAI lab in the School of Software Engineering under the supervision of assistant professor Weibin Wu, and my research is on evaluating deep learning model robustness through adversarial attacks, with the goal of improving AI security.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### **Interns**

TAI Lab, School of Software Engineering, Sun Yat-sen University [ 10/01/2022 - Current ]

City: Zhuhai
Country: China

Evaluating deep learning model robustness through adversarial attacks, with the goal of improving AI security.

### **Executive Supervisor**

[ 01/09/2021 - 02/03/2022 ]

## Citi Cup

This project combines financial knowledge graph and natural language processing technologies to build a graph by analyzing public reports of companies to obtain relevant information and use the resulting information to rate different companies and institutions on ESG.

### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

### B.Eng.

Sun Yat-sen University [ 09/01/2020 - Current ]

Address: Tangqi Road, Xiangzhou District, 519082 Zhuhai (China)

Field(s) of study: Software Engineering

**Final grade: 3.9/5.0** 

- 1. Main Courses: Artificial Intelligence, Operating System, Computer Network, Block Chain, Data Structure, Compiler Principles, Database Design, Software Analysis, Advanced Mathematics, Linear Algebra, Discrete Mathematics and so on.
- 2. Awards:
  - a. Second Prize Scholarship for undergraduates, 2022
  - b. KINGDOM CARES Scholarship, 2022
  - c. Finalist in CUMCM, 2022
  - d. First prize in SYSU-ICPC Novice trial, 2022

### **LANGUAGE SKILLS**

Mother tongue(s): Chinese

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C1

**SPOKEN PRODUCTION** C1 **SPOKEN INTERACTION** C1